// This JS page is for the quiz questions
var questionList = [
    {
        question: "1. Who is the main protaganist in the anime 'Naruto'?",
        choice1 : "Sasuke Uchiha",
        choice2 : "Sakura Haruno",
        choice3 : "Naruto Uzumaki",
        choice4 : "Itachi Uchiha",
        correctAns: "Naruto Uzumaki"
    },
    
    {
        question: "2. Which of these anime series was created by Hayao Miyazaki?",
        choice1 : "Spirited Away",
        choice2 : "Attack on Titan",
        choice3 : "One Piece",
        choice4 : "Dragon Ball Z",
        correctAns: "Spirited Away"
    },
    {
        question: "3. Who is the creator of the anime series 'One Piece'?",
        choice1 : "Masashi Kishimoto",
        choice2 : "Eiichiro Oda",
        choice3 : "Naoko Takeuchi",
        choice4 : "Hayao Miyazaki",
        correctAns: "Eiichiro Oda"
    },
    {
        question: "4. In the anime 'Attack on Titan', what are the giant humanoid creatures that threaten humanity called?",
        choice1: "Giants",
        choice2: "Colossus",
        choice3: "Titans",
        choice4: "Behemoths",
        correctAns: "Titans"
    },
    {
        question: "5. What is the name of Goku's signature attack in the anime series 'Dragon Ball Z'?",
        choice1: "Spirit Bomb",
        choice2: "Kamehameha",
        choice3: "Final Flash",
        choice4: "Special Beam Cannon",
        correctAns: "Kamehameha"
    },
    {
        question: "6. What term is used when a Soul Reaper releases their sword, in the anime series 'Bleach'?",
        choice1: "Haki",
        choice2: "Hakai",
        choice3: "Shikai",
        choice4: "Bankai",
        correctAns: "Bankai"
    },
    {
        question: "7. Which of the following was never Hokage in the anime series 'Naruto'?",
        choice1: "Shikamaru",
        choice2: "Danzo",
        choice3: "Konohamaru",
        choice4: "Kakashi",
        correctAns: "Konohamaru"
    },
    {
        question: "8. Which gear did Luffy use to take down Kaido, in the anime series 'One Piece'?",
        choice1: "Gear 2nd",
        choice2: "Gear 4",
        choice3: "Gear 3rd",
        choice4: "Gear 5",
        correctAns: "Gear 5"
    },
    {
        question: "9. In the anime 'Full Metal Alchemist', when Ed and Al first performed alchemy what was their intention?",
        choice1: "To create a new ice cream flavor",
        choice2: "To acquire a new puppy",
        choice3: "To get their mom back",
        choice4: "To save the world from Father",
        correctAns: "To get their mom back"
    },
    {
        question: "10. In the anime series, 'DBZ', after returning from death who was the first person Cell killed?",
        choice1: "Trunks",
        choice2: "Vegeta",
        choice3: "Goku",
        choice4: "Gohan",
        correctAns: "Trunks"
    }
]